<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="format_year_title">%d format</string>

    <string name="format_qualifying">Qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying">Sprint qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_sprint">Sprint</string>
    <string name="format_race">Race</string>

    <!-- Stats -->
    <string name="format_stats_race_length">Race length</string>
    <string name="format_stats_qualifying_sessions">Number of sessions</string>
    <string name="format_stats_session_length_q1">Q1 session length</string>
    <string name="format_stats_session_length_q2">Q2 session length</string>
    <string name="format_stats_session_length_q3">Q3 session length</string>
    <string name="format_stats_max_laps">Max laps</string>
    <string name="format_stats_fuel_limit">Fuel limit</string>
    <string name="format_stats_mandatory_pit_stop">Mandatory Pit Stop</string>
    <string name="format_stats_fastest_lap_point">Fastest lap point</string>

    <string name="format_stat_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="format_stat_no">No</string>

    <string name="format_qualifying_q1">Q1</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_q2">Q2</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_q3">Q3</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_final">Final grid order</string>

    <string name="format_qualifying_knockout_test">Quailfying uses the knockout format, where drivers have to set competitive lap times in order to qualify for the next round. </string>


    <!-- Qualifying - Knockout -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_knockout">Knockout qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_knockout_summary">Knockout qualifying consists of three rounds (Q1, Q2 and Q3) where the 5 slowest drivers are knocked out at the end of the round until 10 drivers are left in the final round</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_knockout_q2">Drivers who make it into Q3 are required to start the grand prix on the tyres they did their Q2 run on</string>

    <!-- Qualifying - pre-1996 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_two_session">Two Session qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_two_session_summary">Two Session qualifying consists of two rounds (Q1 and Q2) in which their fastest lap time of any session counts towards the qualifying order</string>

    <!-- Qualifying - 1996-2002 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_hour">One Hour qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_hour_summary">One Hour qualifying gave drivers a maximum of 12 laps to do their fastest lap time</string>

    <!-- Qualifying - 2003 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_lap_two_rounds">One Lap qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_lap_two_rounds_summary">One lap qualifying consisted of two sessions (Q1 and Q2) gave drivers only one attempt to set the fastest lap time per round.</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_lap_two_rounds_summary2">The finishing order for Q1 would set the order in which lap times are set in Q2</string>

    <!-- Qualifying - 2004 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_lap">One Lap qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_one_lap_summary">One lap qualifying gave drivers only one attempt to set the fastest lap time possible to get pole position</string>
    
    <!-- Qualifying - 2005 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated">Aggregated qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated_first_6">First 6 races</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated_summary">Aggregated qualifying was a two round format (Q1 and Q2) where the lap times set by drivers in each of the sessions are added together to make the overall lap time</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated_fuel">The first session on the saturday consisted of low fuel running and then the second session on Sunday with race fuel </string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated_remainder">Remaining 13 races</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_aggregated_single">For the remainder of the season, the two rounds were merged into one round on the saturday, where drivers had one attempt to set a lap time on race fuel to decide their position on the grid</string>

    <!-- Qualifying - 2016 -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_elimination">Elimination qualifying</string>
    <string name="format_qualifying_elimination_summary">For the first two races of the season, the format was tweaked slightly where drivers were eliminated at 90s intervals throughout the session instead of at the end of the session.</string>

    <!-- Points -->
    <string name="format_points_title">Points</string>
    <string name="format_points_subtitle">Drivers are awarded the following points for based on their finishing position</string>

    <!-- Qualifying -->
    <string name="format_qualifying_q2_rule">Drivers who make it through to Q3 must start the race on the tyre compound they qualified in Q2 from</string>

    <!-- Sprint -->
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying_summary">Sprint Qualifying weekend events are hosted after the knockout qualifying but before the Grand Prix to set the order for the race.</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying_summary2">The starting order is set by the result of the knockout sprint qualifying held on the friday, with the winner awarded pole position for the race on sunday</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying_summary3">This format was trialled in 2021 for the British Grand Prix, Italian Grand Prix and Brazilian Grand Prix</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying_points">Points</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_qualifying_points_summary">Points are awarded for the final result of sprint qualifying</string>

    <string name="format_sprint_summary">Sprint events are an iteration on the 2021 Sprint Qualifying format, and are hosted after the knockout qualifying but before the Grand Prix to set the order for the race.</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_summary2">The starting order is set by the result of the knockout sprint qualifying held on the friday. The starting position on the grid is decided by the finishing order of the Sprint, but qualifying pole position is awarded to the top finisher in Q3</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_summary3">This format will be trialled in 2022 for the Emilia Romagna Grand Prix, Austrian Grand Prix and Brazilian Grand Prix</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_points">Points</string>
    <string name="format_sprint_points_summary">Points are awarded for the final result of sprint qualifying</string>

    <!-- Race -->
    <string name="format_race_summary">The FIA Formula 1 Grand Prix event usually takes place on the sunday of the grand prix weekend</string>


</resources>