<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- All -->
    <string name="settings_all_title">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_all_appearance">Appearance</string>
    <string name="settings_all_appearance_subtitle">Theme and animation preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_all_home">Home</string>
    <string name="settings_all_home_subtitle">Customise the home screen to your liking</string>
    <string name="settings_all_rss">RSS</string>
    <string name="settings_all_rss_subtitle">Browser and RSS preferences</string>
    <string name="settings_all_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="settings_all_notifications_subtitle">Customise what notifications you receive</string>
    <string name="settings_all_support">Support</string>
    <string name="settings_all_support_subtitle">General app settings for crash reporting, analytics, etc.</string>
    <string name="settings_all_ads">Adverts</string>
    <string name="settings_all_ads_subtitle">Configure how ads are displayed to you</string>
    <string name="settings_all_about">About</string>
    <string name="settings_all_about_subtitle">About Flashback</string>

    <!-- Support -->
    <string name="settings_help">Support</string>
    <string name="settings_help_crash_reporting_title">Crash Reporting</string>
    <string name="settings_help_crash_reporting_description">Send device information and crash stack traces to the developer</string>
    <string name="settings_help_crash_reporting_notify">Your crash reporting preference will be applied once the app has restarted</string>
    <string name="settings_help_analytics_title">Anonymous analytics</string>
    <string name="settings_help_analytics_description">Send anonymous analytics data about your app experience. This can also aid crash reporting</string>
    <string name="settings_help_analytics_notify">Your analytics preference will be applied once the app has restarted</string>
    <string name="settings_help_shake_to_report_title">Shake the app to report a bug or a feature?</string>
    <string name="settings_help_shake_to_report_description">Shake the app at any time to screenshot and send us any bugs, issues, or suggestions you may have for this app!</string>
    <string name="settings_help_shake_to_report_notify">Your shake to report preference will be applied once the app has restarted</string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="settings_about">About</string>
    <string name="settings_about_about_title">About this app</string>
    <string name="settings_about_about_description">About the application and the developer</string>
    <string name="settings_about_review_title">Review</string>
    <string name="settings_about_review_description">Rate the app on the google play store</string>
    <string name="settings_about_release_notes_title">Release notes</string>
    <string name="settings_about_release_notes_description">See the release notes history</string>
    <string name="settings_about_privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="settings_about_privacy_policy_description">View our privacy policy here</string>

    <!-- Send email -->
    <string name="send_email">Send email</string>

    <!-- About -->
    <string name="about_name">Flashback</string>
    <string name="about_desc">Contact Information</string>
    <string name="dependency_thank_you"><b>Contact Email: </b>\nthementalgoose@gmail.com\n\nThe Formula 1 statistics in this app are provided by the Ergast API and cached by the Flashback team. Like the Ergast API, we cannot guarantee the accuracy of the data provided (please let us know however if you spot an issue by sending us an email with the link above)\n\nA big thank you to everyone listed below for making this app possible! Click any one of the items in the list below to find more information about the libraries and services used within the app.</string>
    <string name="about_additional">Special thanks to everyone above! If we\'ve missed anyone or anything please let us know!</string>
    <string name="about_this_app_email">Send Email</string>
    <string name="about_this_app_play">Google Play</string>

    <!-- Privacy Policy -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_title">Privacy Policy</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_data"><![CDATA[<h1>Flashback</h1>
    <p>Jordan Fisher built the Flashback app. This SERVICE is provided by Jordan Fisher at no cost and is intended for use as is.</p>
    <p>This page is used to inform visitors regarding my policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use my Service.</p>
    <p>If you choose to use my Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that I collect is used for providing and improving the Service. I will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.</p>
    <p><strong>Information Collection and Use</strong></p>
    <p>For a better experience, while using our Service, I may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that I request will be retained on your device and is not collected by me in any way.</p>
    <p>The app does use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.</p>
    <p>Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app</p>
    <ul>
        <li><a href="https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/" target="_blank">Google Play Services</a></li>
        <li><a href="https://firebase.google.com/policies/analytics" target="_blank">Firebase Analytics</a></li>
        <li><a href="http://try.crashlytics.com/terms/privacy-policy.pdf" target="_blank">Crashlytics</a></li>
    </ul>
    <p><strong>Log Data</strong></p>
    <p> I want to inform you that whenever you use my Service, in a case of an error in the app I collect data and information (through third party products) on your phone called a crash report. This crash report may include information such as your device Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, device name, operating system version, the configuration of the app when utilizing my Service, the time and date of your use of the Service, and other statistics. You can opt out of this crash reporting in the settings</p>
    <p><strong>Service Providers</strong></p>
    <p> I may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:</p>
    <ul>
        <li>To facilitate our Service;</li>
        <li>To provide the Service on our behalf;</li>
        <li>To perform Service-related services; or</li>
        <li>To assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.</li>
    </ul>
    <p> I want to inform users of this Service that these third parties have access to your Personal Information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they are obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.</p>
    <p><strong>Security</strong></p>
    <p> I value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we are striving to use commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and I cannot guarantee its absolute security. I have taken steps to aid in this security, please feel free to <a href="mailto:thementalgoose@gmail.com">email me</a> if you wish me to provide more information</p>
    <p><strong>Links to Other Sites</strong></p>
    <p>This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by me. Therefore, I strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. I have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.</p>
    <p><strong>Children’s Privacy</strong></p>
    <p>These Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. I do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. In the case I discover that a child under 13 has provided me with personal information, I immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact me so that I will be able to do necessary actions.</p>
    <p><strong>Changes to This Privacy Policy</strong></p>
    <p> I may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. I will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.</p>
    <p><strong>Contact Us</strong></p>
    <p>If you have any questions or suggestions about my Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to <a href="mailto:thementalgoose@gmail.com">contact me at thementalgoose@gmail.com</a> about your issues.</p>
    <p>This privacy policy page was created at <a href="https://privacypolicytemplate.net" target="_blank">privacypolicytemplate.net</a> and modified/generated by <a href="https://app-privacy-policy-generator.firebaseapp.com/" target="_blank">App Privacy Policy Generator</a></p>]]></string>


    <!-- Release Notes -->
    <string name="release_notes_description">Here\'s what\'s changed since you last updated</string>
    <string name="release_notes_title">Release notes</string>

</resources>